<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Nineteenth-Century Criminal Tattoos</title>
    <link>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Nineteenth-Century Criminal Tattoos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Come TogetheR: Combining data tables in R with dplyr join verbs</title>
      <link>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2021/06/19/come-together-combining-data-tables-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2021/06/19/come-together-combining-data-tables-in-r/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Combining data The data Joining with dplyr  inner_join and left_join anti_join and semi_join do stuff inside the join function using multiple variables as a key joining summarised data  Now what? Resources  extending dplyr joins    Introduction Combining or joining data tables using a shared key (or ID) column is crucial for working with many kinds of datasets, but is not often well understood by historians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tidying Tattoos: Handling missing data and non-tidy columns</title>
      <link>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2021/05/15/tidying-tattoos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2021/05/15/tidying-tattoos/</guid>
      <description>What is “tidy data”? The data Missing data  a simple case more complex cases  Multiple values in one cell  a simple case more complex cases  Now what?   What is “tidy data”? “Tidy” data describes data that conforms to three rules:
 Each variable must have its own column. Each observation must have its own row. Each value must have its own cell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A first look at tattoos in the Digital Panopticon</title>
      <link>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2021/04/12/a-first-look-at-tattoos-in-the-digital-panopticon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2021/04/12/a-first-look-at-tattoos-in-the-digital-panopticon/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This post is an introduction to, firstly, the newly-released Tattoos in the Digital Panopticon Database, 1793-1925; and, secondly, to the software and code being used to analyse the data.
The dataset contains about 195,000 physical descriptions of convicts and prisoners. About 75,000 of these have been identified as containing tattoos, representing about 58,000 individuals (according to DP record linkage), and somewhere in the region of 350,000 discrete tattoos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Release: Tattoos in the Digital Panopticon Database, 1793-1925</title>
      <link>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2020/12/21/data-release-tattoos-in-the-digital-panopticon-database-1793-1925/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2020/12/21/data-release-tattoos-in-the-digital-panopticon-database-1793-1925/</guid>
      <description>I’m delighted to be able to announce that we’ve shared the project data under a Creative Commons licence and it’s now available for download from the University of Sheffield data repository:
Tattoos in the Digital Panopticon database, 1793-1925
I’ll be blogging about this soon; here’s a taster of what’s to come…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tattoos Hackathon, 16 April 2019</title>
      <link>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2019/05/21/tattoos-hackathon-16-april-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2019/05/21/tattoos-hackathon-16-april-2019/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Designs: word correlations (selected words) Designs: word correlations Subjects: correlation plot Designs: comparing word use by punishment   Introduction For the project’s data hackathon last month, I put together a few very exploratory slides. I’m currently working on more ideas, but I thought I’d put these up to whet a few appetites.
The data itself is still very much work in progress, so on this occasion I’m not going to share the dataset; sorry, you’ll just have to wait a bit longer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Tattoos Project</title>
      <link>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2018/11/03/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/post/2018/11/03/introduction/</guid>
      <description>The project Data extraction and classification Data analysis and visualisation  The datasets The descriptions Criminal registers Founders and Survivors Registers of Habitual Criminals  Code and data What’s next?   The project This website accompanies the British Academy funded project Criminal Tattoos.
 The remarkable increase in tattooing among convicts in the nineteenth century is poorly understood. It is unclear why convicts marked their bodies in ways which facilitated official surveillance, nor do we understand the complex mixture of sentiments expressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources for R</title>
      <link>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://CriminalTattoos.github.io/resources/</guid>
      <description>These are all (at the time of writing) freely available online resources.
General  CRAN - The Comprehensive R Archive Network RStudio StackOverflow posts tagged [R]  Tutorials getting started  Excel vs R: A Brief Introduction to R - why to use R for data analysis instead of spreadsheets, and how to get started, using a historical source as an example  Programming Historian lessons (a selection):
 R Basics with Tabular Data Basic Text Processing in R Data Wrangling and Management in R  more substantial  R for Data Science - the textbook for &amp;ldquo;Tidy&amp;rdquo; R.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
